♪ If they saw what I saw ♪
♪ They would fall the way I
fell ♪
♪ But they don’t know what you
want ♪
♪ And baby I would never tell ♪
♪ If they knew what I know ♪
♪ They would never let you go ♪
♪ So guess what, I ain’t never
letting you go ♪
♪ Cause your lips were made for
mine ♪
♪ And my heart would go
flatline ♪
♪ If it wasn’t beating for you
all the time ♪
♪ So if I get jealous ♪
♪ I can’t help it ♪
♪ I want every bit of you, I
guess I’m selfish ♪
♪ It’s bad for my mental, but ♪
♪ I can’t fight it, when ♪
♪ You’re out looking like you
do ♪
♪ But you can’t hide it, no ♪
♪ Put you in a frame ooo ♪
♪ Baby who could blame you ♪
♪ Glad your mama made you ♪
♪ Makin’ me insane, you ♪
♪ Cannot be explained ooo ♪
♪ You must be an angel ♪
♪ Every time the phone rings ♪
♪ I hope that it’s you on the
other side ♪
♪ I want to tell you everything♪
♪ Everything that’s on my mind ♪
♪ And I don’t want any other
guys ♪
♪ Taking my place, girl, I got
too much pride ♪
♪ I know I may be wrong, but I
don’t wanna be right ♪
♪ Cause your lips were made for
mine ♪
♪ And my heart could go
flatline ♪
♪ If it wasn’t beating for you
all the time ♪
♪ So if I get jealous ♪
♪ I can’t help it ♪
♪ I want every bit of you, I
guess I’m selfish ♪
♪ It’s bad for my mental, but ♪
♪ I can’t fight it, when ♪
♪ You’re out looking like you
do ♪
♪ But you can’t hide it, no ♪
♪ Put you in a frame ooo ♪
♪ Baby who could blame you ♪
♪ Glad your mama made you ♪
♪ Makin me insane, you ♪
♪ Cannot be explained ooo ♪
♪ You must be an angel ♪
♪ Put you in a frame ooo ♪
♪ Baby who could blame you ♪
♪ Glad your mama made you ♪
♪ Makin me insane, you ♪
♪ Cannot be explained ooo ♪
♪ You must be an angel ♪
♪ Owner of my heart ♪
♪ Tattooed your mark ♪
♪ There for the whole world to
see ♪
♪ You’re the owner of my heart ♪
♪ And all my scars ♪
♪ Baby you got such a hold on
me ♪
♪ So if I get jealous ♪
♪ I can’t help it ♪
♪ I want every bit of you, I
guess I’m selfish ♪
♪ It’s bad for my mental, but ♪
♪ I can’t fight it, when ♪
♪ You’re out looking like you
do ♪
♪ But you can’t hide it, no ♪
♪ Put you in a frame ooo ♪
♪ Baby who could blame you ♪
♪ Glad your mama made you ♪
♪ Makin’ me insane, you ♪
♪ Cannot be explained ooo ♪
♪ You must be an angel ♪
♪ Put you in a frame ooo ♪
♪ Baby who could blame you ♪
♪ Glad your mama made you ♪
♪ Makin’ me insane, you ♪
♪ Cannot be explained ooo ♪
♪ You must be an angel ♪
♪ Jealous, but I can’t help it ♪
♪ I want every bit of you, I
guess I’m selfish ♪